<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conner Chu</title><link>https://connerchu.com/</link><description>Recent content on Conner Chu</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy Copyright 2025</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 23:30:59 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://connerchu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California Great America</title><link>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/cga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 23:30:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/cga/</guid><description>Had the chance to make a quick day trip to San Jose and visit CGA! Definitely a chill park overall, nothing too crazy, though all the rides were fairly bumpy for some reason lol.
RailBlazer - RMC&amp;rsquo;s prototype single rail&amp;hellip;a little rough around the edges! Flight Deck - My first greyout?? Drop Tower - Felt taller than I expected! Patriot - Somewhat smooth yay Gold Striker - Bumpy and noisy like any wooden coaster :/ The Grizzly - Super old station The Demon - Apparently historical Pyscho Mouse - Psycho line Mass Effect: New Earth - Interesting smells&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Photography</title><link>https://connerchu.com/photography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:47:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/photography/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Singular Value Decomposition</title><link>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/svd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/svd/</guid><description>Singular Value Decomposition (SVD) is probably one of the coolest concepts in mathematics I have learned so far. Seen by many as the grand finale of an introductory linear algebra course, SVD combines many pervasive topics seen throughout physics and applied math, including eigenvalues/eigenvectors and unitary matrices. Although SVD was not covered in my introductory mathematical physics course, I tried my best to develop a basic understanding of this factorization tool so that I could comfortably use it when decomposing transient absorption data in my work at the Leone Group.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Polarized Attosecond Transient Absorption Spectroscopy of Elemental Tellurium</title><link>https://connerchu.com/research/atas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/research/atas/</guid><description>This summer, I had the pleasure of working under Jonah Adelman in Prof. Stephen Leone&amp;rsquo;s group at UC Berkeley. Our group specializes in attosecond transient absorption pump-probe spectroscopy via high-harmonic generation, and my lab specifically focuses on applying this technique towards solid-state materials. Over the course of two months, my main objective was familiarizing myself with the first principles governing this spectroscopic method, and to conduct an experiment of my own, namely cross-polarizing the VIS-NIR pump beam and XUV probe beam in our setup to quantify the potential differences in absorption in elemental Tellurium.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://connerchu.com/resume/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/resume/</guid><description>It appears you don't have a PDF plugin for this browser. No biggie... you can click here to download the PDF file.</description></item><item><title>Six Flags Fiesta Texas</title><link>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/sfft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/sfft/</guid><description>Was in Austin and decided to make the hour drive to San Antonio to visit one of Six Flags&amp;rsquo; flagship parks on a day with only ~9% of full capacity!
Iron Rattler - Two massive drops over a quarry wall make it my new favorite RMC. Wonder Woman - As with SFFM, back seat only, trust! Dr. Diabolical&amp;rsquo;s Cliffhanger - 95 degree drop!?! Joker: Carnival of Chaos - Not as crazy as CraZanity :( Superman: Krypton Coaster - Nice scenery Scream!</description></item><item><title>Six Flags Magic Mountain</title><link>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/sfmm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/sfmm/</guid><description>After going to Six Flags Magic Mountain for the second time today, I wanted to make a quick ranking of all the rides I have ridden there (coasters and flats)!
Twisted Colossus - RMC, enough said! X2 - Pure chaos. Wonder Woman - Back seat only, trust me! Tatsu - A secret line and a pretzel&amp;hellip; Drop of Doom - Are we still falling??? CraZanity - I think I&amp;rsquo;m upside down Viper - 5.</description></item><item><title>Earbuds and Airplane Toilets</title><link>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/airplane/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/tidbits/airplane/</guid><description>I do not ride on planes often, but when I do I always think of the same two questions.
Why do I always have to turn the volume of my earbuds higher when I am on an airplane? Is it because of the lower pressure of the cabin compared to the near sea-level altitude that I am used to? Or is it simply because the loud engines drown out the noise of my music?</description></item><item><title>Examining the Growth of Methanotrophic Bacteria Immersed in Extremely Low-Frequency Electromagnetic Fields</title><link>https://connerchu.com/research/jei/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://connerchu.com/research/jei/</guid><description>It was around sophomore year of high school when I first learned about the odd fact that cow farts play a considerable role in the release of methane, a potent greenhouse gas, into our atmosphere. This surprising fact led me down a rabbit hole to understand the causes and effects of climate change. Around the same time, I learned and grew skeptical of a relatively new technology, electromagnetic field therapy, which claimed to boost cell proliferation and nutrient circulation in living systems.</description></item></channel></rss>